<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Braden Fowler&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Braden Fowler&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dogs</title>
      <link>/2020/12/07/dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/12/07/dogs/</guid>
      <description>Dogs Using the data from TidyTuesdays website, I am going to look at dog descriptions, exporting and importing of dgos, and dogs that have traveled. The first data set contains 58,180 observations and 36 variables. The second data set contains 90 observations and 5 variables. The third data set contains 6,194 observations and 8 variables. From these data sets I can see which dogs are better able to perform tricks, which dogs travel more than other dogs, whether these certain dogs are mixed, or purebred, their colors, sex, size, coat length, and many others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Ratings</title>
      <link>/2020/12/07/office-ratings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/12/07/office-ratings/</guid>
      <description>Office Ratings For this project, I am going to be looking at Office Ratings data set contained in the library “schrute” which I installed through R. This data set contains ratings of each episode from the famous US adapted sitcom television series. The data has 55,130 observation and 12 variables. The variable season tells us which season of the show is being selected from. The variable episode tells us which episode of the season is being selected.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
